199.21.148.39 2014-05-30

# Privacy Policy | PPV Pay Per View - Pop Under - Pop Up Ads - Targeted Internet Advertising Services

This Privacy Policy describes what information we gather from you, how we use that information, and what we do to protect it. By using the Site, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this notice.

At InfinityAds, we are committed to protecting your privacy. Any information we collect, such as email addresses, are submitted at the visitor’s will. We do not and will not share any personal information with any third parties unless by governmental order.

Use of Cookies:  
Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s computer hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies make using our Website easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. These cookies are restricted for use only on our Website, and do not transfer any personal information to any other party. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can, however, reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. Please consult the technical information relevant to your browser for instructions. If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of the Website may not function properly or may be considerably slower.

Use of Information:  
InfinityAds uses the information you provide or that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features, information and services found on the Site. We will use your email address, without further consent, for administrative purposes, for customer service purposes, to address intellectual property infringement, rights of privacy, or defamation issues. InfinityAds will not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send promotional messages unless you have opted in or otherwise requested that InfinityAds contact you about the InfinityAds services or other information.

Web Sign-up form  
When a Web Publisher signs a service agreement with InfinityAds, the Web Publisher is also required to provide company and personal identity information, commercial information, technical contact information and customization information to start their contextual advertising services. InfinityAds uses this information to provide services and for payment purposes. If InfinityAds has trouble processing an order, it will use this information to contact the Web Publisher.

Links to External Websites:  
InfinityAds is not responsible for the content or practices of third party websites not owned or controlled by InfinityAds. InfinityAds is also not responsible for any information that you might share with such linked websites. You should refer to each such website’s respective privacy policy and practices prior to disclosing any such information.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or concerns about this Web site, please contact: webmaster@InfinityAds.com
